# **Deepak Oberoi**

deepak@dmarkweb.com +91 9357122333

#### Summary

I am a Full Stack Developer with 10+ years of industry experience. I love challenges and learning new technologies while perfecting existing. While learning never ends. I love finding ways to improve my code and prefer clean code for later references. I feel like Object Oriented Programming brings the whole new perspective to programming paradigm, so I love it. Mostly, I have been a Backend Developer with technologies like PHP/NodeJS but with trends, I learned to work with Frontend JS libs, like ReactJS / VueJS / Angular, etc I have very good organisational skills, agility in self-management, a team player, computer fundamental knowledge, software architecture design and more.

#### **Technical Skills**

My skills incudes but, aren't limited to:

Backend Development using Node.js / PHP7 / Laravel / Symfony

JavaScript, TypeScript, ReactJS, Angular, VueJS, Redux, Vanilla JS

SDLC, TDD, Agile, Scrum, Slack, Oops Programming Fundamentals

Product Development / DevOps / CI-CD / Docker / GIT / AWS / Google Cloud Platform / Server Administration, CRON, CURL

REST API's (Google Cloud/ Maps / Analytics / FB / Many others)

RDBMS, Database Schema Designer and used (MySQL / Couchbase / MongoDB / Redis / FileMaker / JSON)

Mobile Development (iOS/Android) using (React Native / iOS)

Team Leader for several Projects

### **Career History**

## FULL STACK DEVELOPER / TEAM LEAD at dMark Solutions

Jul 2014 - Present (5 years and 2 months)

Brand development, Business Development/Planning, handled projects based on multiple stacks and DB technologies. Learned a wide array of technologies and worked on different platforms. Lead teams to the successful completion of multiple projects (In-House and Remote)

### Full Stack PHP/JS Developer at EXPERTZWEB

Jul 2010 - Aug 2014 (4 years and 1 month)

This was the time to learn to shine. More technologies, I was learning, hungrier I was. Tech Stack was changing every day and that presented a challenge to keep up the pace to learn while working. So, I learned time management and self-management. Worked on distributed systems such as RabbitMQ, CRON Jobs, Backend and Frontend AJAX.

### SR. PHP DEVELOPER at A1 TECHNOLOGY

Jan 2009 - Jun 2010 (1 year and 5 months)

As I learned and moved to a new job. I along with that started learning new things along with my Job. It was all fun along the way. I learned working in larger teams and software development Lifecycle. Above all SCRUM method for regular delivery for testing.

### PHP Developer at SMARTBUZZ INC.

May 2007 - Dec 2008 (1 year and 7 months)

My first full scale job as a PHP developer and this is where I started learning my way into this all. I used to be a JAVA lover, which helped me throughout my learning process.

# **Education**

# Bachelor of Technology (Computing Studies) from Dr Bhimrao Ambedkar

University

Graduated 2007

# **DIPLOMA IN COMPUTERS** from CEDTI

Graduated 2000

### Higher School Certificate from Punjab School Education Board

Graduated 1999

Preparing for IELTS Exams

### Social

### LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/devdeepakoberoi/

### Github

https://github.com/wpconsulate

#### Portfolio

## Some of my Work is listed below

https://lingoeducation.com

https://softbusiness.me

https://schoolinks.com

https://lingoeducation.com

https:// Scribblepost.com

https://jobs.vaco.com/

https://www.albabotanica.com/en/

https://www.bendonlingerie.com.au/

https://www.singer.com

https://ems.danskvagt.dk

https://hillplaceapts.com

https://www.stylefinishdesign.com.au/

APPS (React Native)

BenchFly (iOS)

StriveScan (iOS / Android)

Petmeds4vets (iOS / Android)

Redbox (Backend API)